A Guide to the John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, RG 5 Program Files, Subgroup Grant Files FA1795
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Community Initiatives, 1986-2013; 5; 28.1 Cubic Feet 74 letter document boxes
  - Community Crusade Against Drugs of South Florida Inc., 87-53, 1987 March 27-1988 March 27 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 3034
    Grant 87-53, Community Crusade Against Drugs of South Florida Inc., $5,000, for general support.
  - The Fairchild Tropical Garden, 87-276, 1987 December 15-1988 December 15 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    Knight File Number - 3037
    Grant 87-276, The Fairchild Tropical Garden, $35,000 general support
  - The Foundation Center - Cleveland, 87-264, 1987 December 15-1988 December 15 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Knight File Number - 3040
    Grant 87-264, The Foundation Center - Cleveland, $1,600 for annual membership support.
  - Global Energy Society for Eradication of Poverty and Hunger, 87-271, 1987 December 15-1988 December 15 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    Knight File Number - 3041
    Grant 87-271, Global Energy Society for Eradication of Poverty and Hunger, $100,000 for seed money to develop a headquarters for this association of international scientists devoted to improving the lives of Asians and Africans who lack dependable energy sources and to support the economic development of Akron, Ohio.
  - Interval Brotherhood Homes Corporation, 87-173, 1987 September 25-1988 September 25 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 3044
    Grant 87-173, Interval Brotherhood Homes Corporation, $10,000 for materials to convert a storage facility into an activity services center.
  - The John Bartram Association, 87-246, 1987 December 15-1988 December 15 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 3046
    Grant 87-246, The John Bartram Association, $70,000 to renovate and outfit a historic barn for use as an educational center.
  - National Urban League Inc., 87-225, 1987 December 15-1988 December 15 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    Knight File Number - 3054
    Grant 87-225, National Urban League Inc., $20,000 for annual support.
  - Planned Parenthood of Summit, Portage and Medina Counties, 87-226, 1987 December 15-1988 December 15 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    Knight File Number - 3059
    Grant 87-226, Planned Parenthood of Summit, Portage and Medina Counties, $20,000 for general support.
  - Saint Bernard's Church, 87-98, 1987 June 26-1988 June 26 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 3060
    Grant 87-98, Saint Bernard's Church, $25,000 for restoration and preservation of this historic building a one-time grant.
  - St. Mary Medical Center Foundation, 87-99, 1987 June 26-1988 June 26 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 3061
    Grant 87-99, St. Mary Medical Center Foundation, $25,000 for a community health education program for southeast asian refugees with special emphasis on perinatal care and general nutrition.
  - Summitt County Historical Society, 87-59, 1987 March 27-1988 March 27 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 3064
    Grant 87-59, Summitt County Historical Society, $5,000 to computerize administrative records.
  - The Zoological Society of Florida, 87-17, 1987 March 27-1988 March 27 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    Knight File Number - 3073
    Grant 87-17, The Zoological Society of Floridda, $50,000 to rebuild "Sulawesi Village" the children's petting zoo at Miami metrozoo.
  - Detroit Zoological Society, 86-175, 1987 December 31-1989 December 31 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 3076
    Grant 86-175, Detroit Zoological Society, $500,000 to build a new chimpanzee exhibit.
  - Habitat for Humanity of Greater Akron, Ohio Inc., 87-95, 1987 June 26-1989 June 26 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 3078
    Grant 87-95, Habitat for Humanity of Greater Akron, Ohio Inc., $25,000 to provide seed money for this program which rehabilitates housing for the disadvantaged.
  - High Technology Museum, 86-119, 1986 September 18-1991 September 18 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 3085
    Grant 86-119, High Technology Museum, $1,000,000 a challenge grant to participate in creating the technology center, an educational institution that will promote an understanding and awareness of technology. Creed has asked Larry Jinks to look into this grant and whether the terms of it have been met; no date for reporting back was set. 4/6/89.
  - Community Foundation Inc., 94-216, 1994 September 20-1996 September 20 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 2358
    Grant 94-216, $100,000 for operating support for a new community foundation in Macon, Georgia.
  - Ain Dah Yung (our home) Center, 9900303, 1999 December 17-2000 December 17 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 3113
    Grant 9900303, Ain Dah Yung (our home) Center, $25,000 for operating support and diverse capacity-building activities for an organization that provides shelter and social services for Native Americans.
  - California Community Foundation, 9900322, 1999 December 7-2000 December 7 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    Knight File Number - 4260
    Grant 9900322, California Community Foundation, $142,800 for a non-endowed donor advised fund, of which $140,000 was to be regranted to non-profit organizations in Long Beach.
  - Center for Excellence in Nonprofits, 9900284, 1999 December 7-2000 December 7 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    Knight File Number - 3121
    Grant 9900284, Center for Excellence in Nonprofits, $25,000 for phase two of a pilot project, Wired for Good, designed to enhace the strategic use of technology by nonprofit organizations.
  - Columbus Children, Youth and Family Coalition, 9800107, 1998 June 15-2000 June 15 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 3125
    Grant 9800107, Columbus Children, Youth and Family coalition, $37,200 to develop a strategic plan to prevent youth violence in two low-income neighborhoods, as part of the youth violence prevention/youth development initiative.
  - Council on Foundations, 9700222, 1997 December 9-2000 December 9 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 3128
    Grant 9700222, Council on Foundations, $75,000, for a three-year communications/legislative initiative to involve a public information effort and congressional outreach.
  - Donors Forum of Miami, 9900034, 1999 March 16-2000 March 16 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 3130
    Grant 9900034, Donors Forum of Miami, $20,000 for the south florida promotion of philanthropy initiative.
  - Local Initiatives Support Corporation, 96-314, 1996 December 10-2000 December 10 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    Knight File Number - 3137
    Grant 96-314, Local Initiatives Support Corporation, $4 million for the third and final phase of the National Community Development Initiative (NCDI)
  - Macon Heritage Foundation, 9900289, 1999 December 7-2000 December 7 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    Knight File Number - 3138
    Grant 9900289, Macon Heritage Foundation, $200,000 to rehabilitate 14 substandard houses for sale to low-to-moderate income homeowners.
  - NewTown Macon, 9900117, 1999 June 15-2000 June 15 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 3142
    Grant 9900117, NewTown Macon, $1 million to implement a comprehensive plan to revitalize downtown Macon.
  - Ramsey County Department of Public Health, 97-149, 1997 June 16-2000 June 16 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 2195
    Grant 97-149 Ramsey County Department of Public Health, $63,200.00 for a planning process, as part of the Youth Violence/Youth Development Initiative, that uses youth action teams to help design solutions to youth violence.
  - The Salvation Army of Grand Forks, 9900313, 1999 December 7-2000 December 7 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 3143
    Grant 9900313, The Salvation Army of Grand Forks, $100,000 for capital and start-up costs of a new transitional housing facility for homeless families.
  - White House Fellows Foundation, 1997 September 16-2000 September 16 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 3147
    Grant 97-236, White House Fellows Foundation, $100,000 for bridge funding for the White House Fellows Foundation during a major campaign to increase its endowment.
  - Big Brothers Big Sisters of Greater Miami, 2000 June 13-2001 June 13 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 3150
    Grant 20000103, Big Brothers Big Sisters of Greater Miami, $50,000 to serve as the lead agency in Miami-Dade County for the Governor's Mentoring Initiative.
  - Children's Hospital Medical Center of Akron, 1998 December 8-2001 December 8 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 3154
    Grant 9800253, Children's Hospital Medical Center of Akron, $625,500 to modify and expand the PATHS after-school program, as part of the Youth Violence Prevention/Youth Development Initiative.
  - Saint Paul Riverfront Corporation, 9800077, 1998 June 15-2001 June 15 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 2362
    Grant # 9800077 (Request ID # 9800139) for $240,000 to match a state grant for the restoration of Harriet Island Regional Park.
  - City of Long Beach, Mississippi, 20010047, 2001 March 13-2002 March 13 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    Knight File Number - 3176
    Grant 20010047, City of Long Beach, Mississippi, $25,000 to develop a master plan to revitalize the harbor and main street in the downtown area.
  - Hearth Connection, 20000308, 2000 December 5-2002 December 5 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 3180
    Grant 20000308, Hearth Connection $325,000 for a pilot project to create a system to provide and finance case management, diverse support services and housing for homeless individuals with chronic mental illness, substance abuse and/or HIV/AIDS.
  - University of Miami, 20010098, 2001 June 11-2002 June 11 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 3193
    Grant 20010098, University of Miami, $250,000 for a planning grant to develop a community development plan and establish a community resource center that will serve as the cornerstone of West Coconut Grove's revitalization efforts.
  - Access, Inc., 20020035 [20020063 written on folder] (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 3195
    Grant 20020035, Access, Inc.,$50,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 response.
  - Aid to Victims of Domestic Abuse, 20020059 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 3197
    Grant 20020059, Aid to Victims of Domestic Abuse, $50,000 to aid post-Sept 11 relief effors in Boca Raton.
  - Akron Community Service Center & Urban League, 20020036 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 3198
    Grant 20020036, Akron Community Service Center & Urban League, $100,000 to aid post-Sept 11 relief efforts in Akron.
  - Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank, 20020037 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 3199
    Grant 20020037, Akron-Canton Regional Foodbank, $100,000 to aid post-Sept 11 relief efforts in Akron.
  - Arab Community Center for Economic and Social Services, 20020101 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    Knight File Number - 3200
    Grant 20020101, Arab Community Center for Economic and Social Services, $100,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Detroit.
  - Bibb County Department of Family and Children Services, 20020379, 2002 December 10-2003 December 10 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    Knight File Number - 3201
    Grant 20020379, Bibb County Department of Family and Children Services, $82,000 to develop a case management system that increases service collaboration and client tracking for pregnant and parenting teens enrolled in Macon's Teen Parent Center.
  - Big Bend Cares, 20020249 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    Knight File Number - 3202
    Grant 20020249, Big Bend Cares, $10,000 to aid post-Sept 11 relief efforts in Tallahassee.
  - Big Brothers Big Sisters of Greater Miami, 20020274 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    Knight File Number - 3203
    Grant 20020274, Big Brothers Big Sisters of Greater Miami, $30,000 to aid post-Sept 11 relief efforts in Miami.
  - Big Brothers Big Sisters of the Sun Coast, 20020362, 2002 December 10-2003 December (Box 68, Folder 10)
    Knight File Number - 3204
    Grant 20020362, Big Brothers Big Sisters of the Sun Coast, $101,560 to provide mentoring programs to children at Sara Scott Harllee Middle School and Louise R. Johnson Middle School.
  - Boulder County Safehouse, 20020065 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    Knight File Number - 3205
    Grant 20020065, Boulder County Safehouse, $21,930 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief effort in Boulder.
  - Boys and Girls Clubs of Fort Wayne, 20020137 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    Knight File Number - 3286
    Grant 20020137, Boys and Girls Clubs of Fort Wayne, IN, $25,000 to aid post-Sept 11 relief efforts in Ft. Wayne.
  - Boys and Girls Clubs of the Gulf Coast, 20020051 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    Knight File Number - 3206
    Grant 20020051, Boys and Girls Clubs of the Gulf Coast, $10,000 to aid post-Sept 11 relief efforts in Biloxi.
  - Boys and Girls Clubs of Long Beach, 20020157 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    Knight File Number - 3207
    Grant 20020157, Boys and Girls Clubs of Long Beach, $70,000 to aid post-Sept 11 relief efforts in Long Beach..
  - Brehon Institute for Human Services, 20020250 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 3208
    Grant 20020250, Brehon Institute for Human Services, $10,000 to aid post-Sept 11 relief efforts in Tallahassee.
  - Broward Coalition for the Homeless, 20020168 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 3209
    Grant 20020168, Broward Coalition for the Homeless, $35,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Miami.
  - CASA of Aberdeen Fifth Judicial Circuit, 20020032 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 3210
    Grant 20020032, CASA of Aberdeen Fifth Judicial Circuit, $25,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Aberdeen.
  - Catholic Charities, 20020138 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 3211
    Grant 20020138, Catholic Charities, $10,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Fort Wayne.
  - Catholic Charities of the Archdiocese of Miami, 20020170 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 3212
    Grant 20020170, Catholic Charities of the Archdiocese of Miami, $125,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Miami.
  - Catholic Charities of Santa Clara County, 20020213 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    Knight File Number - 3213
    Grant 20020213, Catholic Charities of Santa Clara County, $35,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in San Jose.
  - Center Against Sexual and Domestic Abuse, 20020128 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    Knight File Number - 3214
    Grant 20020128, Center Against Sexual and Domestic Abuse, $5,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief effort in Duluth.
  - Centre County Women's Resource Center, 20020246 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    Knight File Number - 3215
    Grant 20020246, Centre County Women's Resource Center, $35,000 to aid post-Sept.11 efforts on State College.
  - Children's Haven and Adult Community Services, 20020070 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    Knight File Number - 3216
    Grant 20020070, Children's Haven & Adult Community Services, $40,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Bradenton.
  - Clara-Mateo Alliance, 20020215 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    Knight File Number - 3217
    Grant 20020215, Clara-Mateo Alliance, $10,000 to aid post-Sept 11 relief efforts in San Jose.
  - Committee for Dignity and Fairness for the Homeless Housing, 20020198 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    Knight File Number - 3218
    Grant 20020198, Committee for Dignity and Fairness for the Homeless Housing, $100,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Philadelphia.
  - Community Action Council for Lexington, 20020155 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 3219
    Grant 20020155, Community Action Council for Lexington, $100,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Lexington.
  - Community Building Initiative, 20000328, 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 3220
    Grant 20000328, Community Building Initiative, $120,000 for the Leadership Development Initiative, a project engaging community leaders in addressing issues of racial and ethnic inclusion.
  - Crisis Assistance Ministry, 20020080 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    Knight File Number - 3224
    Grant 20020080, Crisis Assistance Ministry, $150,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Charlotte.
  - Detroit Rescue Mission Ministries, 20020106 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 3227
    Grant 20020106, Detroit Rescue Mission Ministries, $75,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Detroit.
  - Emergency Family Assistance Association, 20020067 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 3230
    Grant 20020067, Emergency Famiily Assistance Association, $33,520 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Boulder.
  - Emergency Housing Consortium of Santa Clara County, 20020220 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 3231
    Grant 20020220, Emergency Housing Consortium of Santa Clara County, $35,000 To aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in San Jose.
  - The Family Center, 20020083 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 3232
    Grant 20020083, The Family Center, $25,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Charlotte.
  - Family Service Center of SC, 20020090 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    Knight File Number - 3233
    Grant 20020090, Family Service Center of SC, $50,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Columbia.
  - Food Bank of State College, 20020247 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    Knight File Number - 3234
    Grant 20020247, Food Bank of State College, $20,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in State College.
  - God's Pantry Food Bank, 20020156 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 3237
    Grant 20020156, God's Pantry Food Bank, $50,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Lexington.
  - Greater Philadelphia Food Bank, 20020203 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 3238
    Grant 20020203, Greater Philadelphia Food Bank, $150,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Philadelphia.
  - The Greater Philadelphia Urban Affairs Coalition, 20020204 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 3239
    Grant 20020204, The Greater Philadelphia Urban Affairs Coalition, $150,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Philadelphia.
  - Guadalupe Clinic, 20020266 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 3240
    Grant 20020266, Guadalupe Clinic, $25,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Wichita.
  - Harvest Hope Food Bank, 20020092 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 3241
    Grant 20020092, Harvest Hope Food Bank, $75,000 to aid post-Sept.11 relief efforts in Columbia.
  - HOPE Family Services, 20020071 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    Knight File Number - 3243
    Grant 20020071, HOPE Family Services, $20,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Bradenton.
  - The Horace Mann-Ambridge Neighborhood Improvement, 20020150 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    Knight File Number - 3244
    Grant 20020150, The Horace Mann-Ambridge Neighborhood Improvement, $50,000 to aid post Sept. 11 relief efforts in Gary.
  - House of T.I.M.E.,20020096 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    Knight File Number - 3245
    Grant 20020096, House of T.I.M.E.$40,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 efforts in Columbus.
  - Inter-Faith Ministries Wichita, 20020268 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 3247
    Grant 20020268, Inter-Faith Ministries Wichita, $15,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Wichita.
  - Jewish Family Service, 20020115 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 3248
    Grant 20020115, Jewish Family Service, $75,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Detroit.
  - LEAP/Center for Strategic Urban Community Leadership, 20020392, 2002 December 10-2003 December 10 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 4343
    Grant 20020392, LEAP/Center for Strategic Urban Community Leadership for $157,300 to develop and pilot test a plan to improve early literacy education in child care centers in Camden.
  - Lifetrack Resources, 20020243 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 3249
    Grant 20020243, Lifetrack Resources, $25,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in St. Paul.
  - Long Beach Day Nursery, 20020159 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    Knight File Number - 3251
    Grant 20020159, Long Beach Day Nursery, $50,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Long Beach.
  - Longmont Coalition for Women in Crisis, 20020069 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    Knight File Number - 3252
    Grant 20020069, Longmont Coalition for Women in Crisis, $12,340 to aid post-Sept.11 11 relief efforts in Boulder.
  - The Lord's Place and Family Shelter West Palm Beach, 20020062 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    Knight File Number - 3253
    Grant 20020062, The Lord's Place and Family Shelter West Palm Beach, $15,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Boca Raton.
  - Lutheran Social Services, 20020141 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    Knight File Number - 3254
    Grant 20020141, Lutheran Social Services, $20,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Fort Wayne.
  - Macon Outreach at Mulberry, 20020165 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    Knight File Number - 3255
    Grant 20020165, Macon Outreach at Mulberry, $25,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Macon.
  - Mental Health Association of Mississippi, 20020054 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    Knight File Number - 3256
    Grant 20020054, Mental Health Association of Mississippi, $20,000 to aid post-Sept. 11 relief efforts in Biloxi.
  - Middle Georgia Community Food Bank, 20020166 (September 11th Fund), 2002 February 18-2003 February 18 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    Knight File Number - 3257